# Ray Youtzy

## 437 375 1799 | raymi.youtzy@gmail.com

### Summary

With these past years, I want to better educate myself of all the different opportunities you get in life. I want to experience the difference ways to enjoy life and bring that joy to others. From the person who cashes you out at the grocery store, to someone who cuts your hair and shows you how beautiful you already are. Thank you

## Experience

Barber/Hairstylist, Self-employed	[2014-2021]
Makeup Artist, Self-employed	[2014-2021]
Video Editor, Freelance, Toronto	[2019-2021]
Youth Transition Coordinator, AIDS Committee of Durham Region, Ontario	[2017-2019]
Canvasser, TNI The Network Inc, Toronto	[2016-2017]
Seamstress, JP Taylor, Oshawa	[2012-2013]
Cashier, Real Canadian Superstore, Oshawa	[2010-2013]

#### Education

Cosmetologist, Hairstylist/Makeup Artist, Career School of Hair and Nails, Oshawa, [2013-2014]
Ontario

• Diploma/Certified: Eyelash Extensions, Makeup, Elumen, Hair Extension

Video/Photo, Media Arts, M. Paul Dwyer Catholic High School, Oshawa, Ontario [2010-2013]

[2013-2021]

• Learned: Final Cut Pro (short films, YouTube, movie trailers), Photoshop.

## Community Service

Volunteer, AIDS Committee of Durham Region, Oshawa, Ontario when I was a child a dear friend of mine passed away and I wanted to give back to the committee in honor of them. I've since been volunteering my time whenever I get the chance from x-mas dinner to helping workshops.

Reference Available Upon Request